<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>KILab🚀</title><link>https://kilab.site/posts/</link><description>Recent content on KILab🚀</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en</language><copyright>© 2025 Knowledge Intelligince Lab @ SYSU.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://kilab.site/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>D-Judge: How Far Are We? Accessing the Discrepancies Between AI-synthesized Images and Natural Images through Multimodal Guidance</title><link>https://kilab.site/posts/djudge/</link><pubDate>Wed, 30 Jul 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kilab.site/posts/djudge/</guid><description>&lt;p>This paper introduces DJudge, a comprehensive benchmark for evaluating the gap between AI-generated and natural images across multiple dimensions including quality, semantic alignment, and human perception.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>🎊 Official Lab Website Launched</title><link>https://kilab.site/posts/website-launch/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kilab.site/posts/website-launch/</guid><description>&lt;p>After careful design and development, the official website of the Knowledge Intelligence Lab (KILab) at Sun Yat-sen University is now fully upgraded and online! The new website adopts modern design concepts, providing visitors with a clearer and more intuitive browsing experience.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Continuous Expansion of International Collaboration Network</title><link>https://kilab.site/posts/international-collaboration/</link><pubDate>Sat, 15 Jun 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kilab.site/posts/international-collaboration/</guid><description>&lt;p>The KILab has always adhered to the concept of open cooperation, establishing extensive and deep collaborative relationships with renowned academic institutions and technology companies worldwide.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Rich Academic Achievements in 2023</title><link>https://kilab.site/posts/academic-achievements-2023/</link><pubDate>Sun, 31 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kilab.site/posts/academic-achievements-2023/</guid><description>&lt;p>2023 was a fruitful year for the KILab. We published high-quality papers at multiple top international academic conferences, demonstrating our research capabilities across various fields of artificial intelligence.&lt;/p></description></item><item><title>Professor Ziyu Lyu Joins SYSU School of Cyber Science and Technology</title><link>https://kilab.site/posts/professor-joins-sysu/</link><pubDate>Fri, 01 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://kilab.site/posts/professor-joins-sysu/</guid><description>&lt;p>We are pleased to announce that Professor Ziyu Lyu officially joined the School of Cyber Science and Technology at Sun Yat-sen University in September 2023, serving as Associate Professor and Ph.D. Supervisor.&lt;/p></description></item></channel></rss>